Mellonee V. Burnim Collection, 1861-1996, bulk 1976-1996 SC 7
Archives of African American Music and Culture
- 3. Smithsonian Institution American Folklife Festival, 1984; 4 Videocassettes 7 hours, 51 minutes
  - Philadelphia Stage, 1984 July 17; VC 546; 1 Videocassette: sound, color; 1/2 in.; (105 minutes)
    Hip Hop Performers from Philadelphia (10 minutes)
    Alaskan Folk Music (10 minutes)
    Alaskan Hula Dancers (11 minutes)
    Alaskan Folk Music (8 minutes)
    Female Gospel Group from Philadelphia (24 minutes)
    Traditional Dance Styles - Southwest Alaska (8 minutes)
    Tap Dancers - Male and Female (18 minutes)
    Hip Hop MCs (Rappers and Breakdancers) from Philadelphia (16 minutes)
- 4. Gospel Sheet Music and Song Texts, approximately 1861-1981; 39 Items
  - Bless this House, ©1927; Taylor, Helen; Brahe, May; 1 Score
  - Born Again, undated; 1 Page text only
  - Bring a Torch, Jeannette, Isabella, undated; 1 Score
  - Come, Ye Disconsolate, undated; James, Will; 1 Score
  - Create in Me a Clean Heart, O God, ©1941; Mueller, Carl; 1 Score
  - Easter, ©1861; Palestrina, G.P.; Monk, William; 1 Score
  - Flammer Choral Series, undated; Richter, Willy; 1 Score
  - Glory Be to God, undated; 1 Score
  - God Is, ©1976; Fryson, Robert; 1 Score
  - God Is Standing By, 1967; 1976 (arranged); Dixon, Jessy; Hawkins, Walter; 1 Score
  - Have to Go By Myself, undated; 1 Page text only
  - He Will Carry You Through, ©1944; Palmer, R.H.; Martin, Robert; 1 Score
  - He'll Supply, ©1979; Davis, Sam; 1 Score
  - He's the Joy of My Salvation, ©1965; Morris, Kenneth; 1 Score
  - Holy, Holy, Holy, undated; 1 Page text only
  - I Don't Know Why, undated; 1 Page text only
  - I Learned How to Lean, undated; 1 Page text only
  - I Walk with God, undated; 1 Page text only
  - I'm So Glad that Jesus, undated; 1 Page text only
  - I've Decided to Make Jesus My Choice, undated; 1 Page text only
  - Jesus Is the Light, undated; 1 Page text only
  - Just Like Fire Shut Up in My Bones, ©1981; Norwood, Dorothy; Morris, Kenneth; 1 Score
  - Let Not Your Heart Be Troubled, undated; Speaks, Oley; Chaffin, Lucien; 1 Score
  - Let There Be Peace on Earth, ©1955; Miller, Sy; Jackson, Jill; 1 Score
  - Looking for a Miracle, undated; 1 Score
  - The Lord Is Holy, undated; 1 Page text only
  - Make Me Over, undated; 1 Page text only
  - My Expectation, undated; 1 Score
  - My God Can Do Anything, undated; 1 Page text only
  - Open Our Eyes, ©1959; Lumpkins, Leon; Morris, Kenneth; 1 Score
  - Prepare Me, undated; 1 Page text only
  - Rise in Thy Goodness, undated; 1 Page text only
  - Rough Side of the Mountain, undated; 1 Page text only
  - Thank You Good Lord Jesus, undated; 1 Page text only
  - Unseen Dangers, undated; 1 Page text only
  - Waiting at the River, undated; 1 Score
  - We Are Not Ashamed, undated; 1 Page text only
  - We Shall Overcome, undated; 1 Page text only
  - With a Voice of Singing, ©1923; Shaw, Martin; 1 Page text only